设备齐全
Comes fully equipped.
告诉你  这是400元钱的便宜价
I'm telling you, it's a steal at $400.
-怎么  要和你丈夫商量吗  -只有我
- What, you gotta check with your husband? - It's just me.
我能拿25美分买自动贩卖机里的东西吗
Can I have a quarter for the vending machine?
宝贝  我说了在泳池边等我
Honey, I said wait for me by the pool.
你说"只有我"
I thought you said it was "just me."
我是指我丈夫不在
I meant my husband's out of the picture.
-只有我和我儿子  -我不知道
- It's just me and my son. - I don't know.
我们大多数房客都不想有噪音
Most of the other tenants--they don't like noise.
他很安静
He's very quiet.
你要预付两个月的房租
I'm gonna need two months up front.
给你  宝贝
Here, honey.
别跑  听见了吗  Miles
Hey, no running. you hear me, Miles?
妈妈  妈妈  救命
Mom! Mommy! Help!
妈妈
Mommy!
Miles  怎么了
Miles, what happened?
妈妈
Mommy!
天啊
Oh, god.
Vonner先生
Mr. Vonner.
你在这做什么
What were you doing in here?
他很孤身一人  他很害怕
He... He was all alone. He was scared.
他胸腔疼  他一直在叫Kimberly
His chest hurt. He kept calling out for Kimberly.
Kimberly  是他妻子
Kimberly? That's his wife.
不  她去年就死了  你怎么知道的
No, she died last year. Now how would you know that?
-我听他说的  -Miles  你在说什么
- I heard him. - Miles, what are you talking about?
他现在还在说话
He's still talking right now.
宝贝
Honey...
他死了
He's dead.
我告诉你  我能听见他说话
I told you! I can hear him!
我能听见
I can hear him!
Miles  你在吗  快接听
Miles, you there? Pick up.
-Jim你到底在哪  -我一会告诉你
- Jim, where the hell are you? - I'll fill you in later.
-我现在要你做件事  -什么
- Right now I need you to take care of something. - Like what?
高压电架里的监控录像带
The security tapes from the pylon camera feeds.
它们要被意外地抹掉
They need to accidentally get erased.
抹掉  为什么
Erased? Why?
我没时间回答  Miles  照做
I ain't got time for questions, Miles. Just do it.
-好的好的  哪些  -看你的监视屏
-Okay. Okay.Uh, which ones? - Look on your monitors.
看见我们了吗
You see us?
看见了  你们在4号
Yeah. you're on number 4.
那是Kate吗  你们到底在做什么
Is that kate? What the hell are you doing out there?
抹掉4号的记录  如果有人问起  就说我不在
Just erase number 4. and if anyone asks, I'm off the grid.
我在找逃跑的敌人
I'm looking for the escaped hostile.
你的朋友Sayid吗
You mean your pal Sayid?
可恶  Miles  你到底帮不帮我
Damn it, Miles! You gonna help me or not?!
-好的  我知道了  -好的  我欠你个人情
-Yeah, Yeah. I got it. - All right. I owe you one.
好的  我要你回去找Juliet
All right, I want you to go back and and find Juliet,
看看有没有人发现小Ben失踪了
See if anyone's noticed yet if little Ben's gone missin'.
如果他们发现了  你怎么办
What are you gonna do when they find out?
尽量瞒过去  提醒你一下
Do my best to cover it up. In case you haven't noticed,
我是保卫部部长
I'm the head of security.
好的  回见
All right, I'll see you back there.
Lafleur在哪
Where's Lafleur?
他出去找越狱的家伙了
Uh, he's, uh, out looking for the escaped prisoner.
我尝试用对讲机联系他  但
I tried to get him on his walkie, but...
-他不在信号范围  -可恶
- Uh, he must be out of range. - Damn it.
好吧  那就只有你来了
All right. then it's gonna have to be you.
Jim已经知道这事了 但我要让你加入信任圈
Jim already knows about this, But I'm gonna bring you into the circle of trust.
我能信任你吗  Miles
Can I trust you, Miles?
当然  Horace
Absolutely, Horace.
很好
Okay. Good.
我要你带这个去坐标3-3-4找Radzinsky
I need you to take this out to Radzinsky at grid 3-3-4.
他会让你带个东西回来的
He's gonna give you something in return.
我要你带来给我  不要问问题
I want you to bring it back to me with no questions asked.
明白吗
You understand?
我们不该去3-3-4
We're not supposed to be in 3-3-4.
那不是敌人的领域吗
Isn't that hostile territory?
欢迎来到信任圈
Welcome to the circle of trust.
在那停下
Stop right there!
MIles  你来这做什么
Miles? what are you doing out here?
我来找Lafleur
I was expecting Lafleur.
Lafleur正忙  Horace派我来替他
Lafleur's busy. Horace sent me instead.
-我在信任圈  -出来
- I'm in the circle of trust. - Get out.
我该给你这个
I'm supposed to give you this.
而你有东西要给我
And said you had something for me.
他怎么了
What happened to him?
出了个意外
He had an accident.
-什么意外  -他掉进了个沟里
- What kind of accident? - He fell into a ditch.
他头上那个是弹孔吗
Is that a bullet hole in his head?
难道那个沟有枪吗
The ditch had a gun?
他发生了什么不重要
It doesn't matter what happened to him
你不需要知道那个
Because knowing that is not your job.
你要做的是听我的指挥
Your job is to do what I tell you to.
Miles  现在带他去Horace那里
Take him back to Horace now, Miles.
好的
Okay...
究竟出了什么事
So what really happened?
本字幕由 YYeTs人人影视 原创翻译制作
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
翻译：  zhjing  非燕  冰卡  傻蛐蛐
校对：  Afan  非燕  zhjing  许愿　   时间轴： GGYY&非燕
■
后期: 冰蚕    剧集总监： 非燕
我找她
I need to see her.
妈
Ma?
是我
It's me.
Miles
Miles.
我很抱歉
I'm--I'm sorry that...
我没能早点来
I couldn't make it by sooner.
没关系
It's okay.
你现在来了
You're here now.
你为什么来  Miles
Why did you come, Miles?
你想要你告诉我
I need you to tell me
为什么我是这样的
Why I'm this way...
我怎么做出那些事的
How... how I do the things I do.
我还想知道你为什么不和我说爸的事
And I need to know why you won't talk to me about my father.
因为他从不关心我们
Because he never cared about us...
从不关心你
Never cared about you.
我要知道他在哪里  -这不重要
- I need to know where he is, ma. - It doesn't matter where.
-重要  -Miles  求你了
- It does matter. - Miles, please.
-我有权知道  -他死了
- I have a right to know! - He's dead.
你爸
Your father...
在你还是个婴儿时  把我们撵了出去
Kicked us out when you were just a baby.
他不想和我们有关系
He didn't want anything to do with us.
你对他知道的越少
So the less you knew about him,
就越好
The better.
你为什么没有告诉我
Why didn't you just tell me?
因为这结束了
Because it was over.
你爸死很久了
Your dad has been dead a long time.
他葬在哪
Where's his body?
你永远去不了的地方
Somewhere you can never go.
Pierre  如果这是电磁导致的
Pierre, if it was caused by the electromagnetism,
我们需要知道
We need to know.
你现在想看吗  他刚回来
You wanna see it now? Yeah, he just got back.
我这就叫他带上它出发  好的
I'll send him out with it right away. Okay.
你带包裹来了吗
Did you bring the package?
"包裹"  你是指死尸吧
"package"? You mean the corpse?
是的  我现在要你带去给兰花站的张博士
Yeah. Now I need you to bring it out to Dr.Chang at the Orchid.
听着  我是保卫部的
Listen, man. I'm security.
如果你只要有人开车
If you just need somebody to drive the van,
车辆调配场的人也可以
Can't someone from the motor pool do it?
如果我要车辆调配厂的人
If I wanted someone from the motor pool,
我就去叫他们了
I would have asked them.
从Lefleur失踪  我就只有你了
And since Lafleur decided to disappear, you're all I've got.
带去给张博士
So just bring it out to Dr. Chang,
今天就这样了  好吗
And we'll all call it a day. okay?
你在做什么  那是我的车
Hey! What the hell are you doing?! That's my van!
刚转到我名下
Nah, dude, I just signed it out.
不管  这是我的
Doesn't matter. it's mine.
-你去哪  -兰花站
- Well, where you going? - The orchid.
我也是  我给他们做了午餐  三明治
Me. too. I made lunch for the crew. Sandwiches.
你要吗  火腿和芝士和秘制的洋葱蛋黄酱
Want one? Ham and cheese, and I made my secret garlic mayo.
你等下辆车吧
You're waiting for the next van.
为什么  我们去同一个地方  为什么不拼车呢
Why? we're going to the same place. Why don't we carpool?
帮助防止现在还没发生的全球变暖
It'll help with global warming, which hasn't happened yet,
我们或许可以防止它发生
So maybe we can prevent it.
-等等  你是在做秘密任务吗  -进来吧
- Wait a sec. Are you on some kind of secret mission? - Just get in.
怎么样了
How'd it go?
我们把他交给小岛居民了
We gave him to them-- to the others.
-有人看见你了吗  -我想没有
- Anyone see you? - I don't think so.
James帮忙了吗
Did James help?
帮了  非常感谢你让他来
Yes. Thank you so much for sending him.
不客气
Of course.
我尽快过来了
I got here as soon as I could.
车子都走了  所以我
All the vans were out, so I had to ru--
Ben去哪了
Where's Ben?
-没有  Roger  -那他在哪里
- No, Roger. - Then where is he?
Roger  抱歉  我离开了10分钟  我不清楚
Roger, i-i'm so sorry. i-i was gone for ten minutes.I-i-i don't know.
什么  你说他生命垂危  怎么还会跑了
What? you--you said he was dying. how could he be gone?
我不知道
I don't know!
-Roger  -她在说什么鬼话  他就这样自己走了吗
I'm--roger-- what is she telling me, that he just got up and walked out?
我不知道
I don't know.
你们是他的医生  应该看好他
I just got-- you're his doctors! you're supposed to watch him!
-我知道  Roger  我们该冷静下来  -别叫我冷静
- I know. I know. roger, if we just calm down- Don't tell me to calm down!
-有人来带走我的人吗  -我了解你的心情  抱歉
- Somebody came and took my boy out of here?! - I know. I am so sorry.
我要去监控室看录像
I'm going to security.
这下可好了
Here we go.
"赏金猎人"怎么拼
How do you spell "bounty hunter"?
你在干什么  写回忆录吗
What are you doing, writing your memoirs?
这是隐私
It's personal.
兄弟
Dude...
你是不是...
Did you just... you know?
怎么
What?
好臭  你有没有
It stinks. did you...
没有
No.
不是我放的
Well, it wasn't me.
那就把车窗摇下
So roll down your window.
算了  是从车里发出的臭味
Nah, man, there's something foul in here.
从后面传来的  可能是三明治的大蒜味
It's coming from back there. maybe it's your famous garlic mayo.
不可能
Unh-unh. that's not possible.
好吧  有可能  停车  我去检查
Okay, maybe it is possible. pull over. I gotta check.
算了吧  你有幻想症  我去检查
Forget it. you're imagining things. I gotta check.
如果那些三明治变质了  人吃了就会生病
If those sandwiches are bad, people could get sick.
能不能停车
Will you pull over?!
兄弟  这里有个装尸袋
Dude, there's a body bag back here.
-里面有具尸体  -装尸袋里都装尸体
- There's a body in it. - That's traditionally what you put in a body bag.
这人是谁  发生了什么事
Yeah, well, who is he? what happened?
这你就不用操心了  也别告诉别人
Don't worry about it and don't tell anybody you saw him.
兄弟  他怎么了
Dude, what happened to him?
他叫Alvarez
His name's Alvarez.
当时在挖洞
He was digging a hole
脑子里在想个叫Andrea的女人
And thinking about some chick named Andrea.
然后他感到口腔一阵剧痛
Then he felt this sharp pain in his mouth,
然后牙齿中产生了一种填充物
Which turned out to be a filling from his tooth
从牙缝中被拔了出来
Being yanked right out of its socket and...
然后猛地进入了他的脑
Blowing through his brain.
然后他就死了
Then he was dead.
一种填充物如何能猛地进入人脑
How does a filling get blown through someone's head?
你知道我的小秘密了  可以走了吗
Got me. can we go now?
你怎么知道这些
How do you know all this?
因为  我本来就知道
Because... I know.
对  可你怎么知道他的思想活动
Yeah, but how do you know what he was thinking?
我就是知道
I just know.
你可以和亡者交流
You can talk to dead people.
我们可以走了吗
Can we please just go?
别担心  兄弟  我会守口如瓶
Don't worry, dude. your secret's safe with me.
-想知道为什么吗  -不想
- You wanna know why? - No.
因为我也可以和他们对话
'cause I can talk to 'em, too.
Gray先生  如果你不介意的话
If you don't mind, mr. Gray,
能告诉我他身上发生了什么事吗
Can you tell me what happened to him?
上个劳动节周末
Last labor day weekend,
醉酒司机闯了红灯
Drunk driver ran the light.
就这样丢了命
That was that.
你儿子埋在哪里
Where is your son buried?
我们把他火葬了
We cremated him,
然后把他的骨灰洒在了学校足球场
Scattered the ashes on the football field at school.
我力所能及的是  最好有具尸体
For what I do, it's much better if there's a body.
可你打的广告上说你可以和亡者交流
Oh, but your ad said you could communicate with the dead
无论何时  无论何地
Anytime, anywhere.
-我知道我的广告标语  Gray先生  可  -拜托
- I-i know what my ad says, mr. Gray, but- Please.
我只想让你问他
I just want you to ask him...
他知道我爱他吗
Did he know that I loved him?
需要另外收费
It's gonna cost extra.
好的
Of course.
谢谢
Thank you.
好  现在
Okay, now...
把手给我
Please give me your hands.
我要你集中注意想Russell
I want you to concentrate on Russell.
在脑海中浮现出他的画面
Just get a picture of him in your head.
-能做到吗  -能
- Can you do that? - Yeah. okay.
有效果吗
Did it work?
你儿子说他知道你爱他
Your son says he knew that you loved him.
他心里一直都很清楚
He always knew.
-谢谢  -对于你儿子的死  我很遗憾
- Thank you. - I'm sorry for your loss.
请问
Excuse me.
-你是Miles Straume吗  -是
- Miles Straume? - Yeah.
你好  我叫Naomi Dorrit
Hi. my name's Naomi Dorrit.
我的老板已经对你的工作追踪了一段时间
My employer's been following your work for some time now,
他对你的独特本领很感兴趣
And he's interested in retaining your rather unique services.
离这不远有家餐馆
There's a restaurant not too far from here.
你有兴趣听我详细说说吗
Would you like to hear what I have to say?
好  当然可以
Yeah. absolutely.
Roger
Hi, roger.
你还好吧
You okay?
让我想想
Let me see...
我儿子中枪了
Well, my son got shot
然后他离奇失踪
And now he's disappeared, so...
我想我心情糟透了
I think I'm pretty far from okay.
我肯定
You know, I'm sure...
一切都会有转机
Things are gonna work out.
谢谢你的鼓舞之词
Well, thanks for the pep talk.
我只是有中感觉  他会相安无事
I just have a feeling he's gonna be okay.
什么意思  感觉
What do you mean, a feeling?
我只是觉得你不该放弃希望
I just don't think that you should give up hope.
你是不是知道其中隐情
Do you know something?
-你知道我儿子的下落吗  -不  我不知道
- Do you know what happened to my son? - No, I don't.
等等
Wait a minute.
你怎么对我孩子那么感兴趣
Why are you so interested in my kid?
我很抱歉过来和你说话
You know, I'm sorry I came over here, all right?
你只是想帮忙  你想帮忙吗  Kate
Oh, you're trying to help, huh? you wanna help, Kate?
你何不管好自己的分内事
Well, why don't you just mind your own business?
我不懂你为什么不肯承认
I don't know why you just won't admit it.
你可以相信我  我和很多死者交谈过
You can trust me. I talk to lots of dead people.
你和他们交谈  就好像他们是你的朋友吗
So you have conversations with them, like they're your pals?
对  自始至终都这样  有时我们还对弈
Sure, all the time. sometimes we even play chess.
你亲眼见到他们吗
You actually see them?
-当然  为什么见不到  -因为不会见到
- Of course. why wouldn't i? - Because that's not how it works.
除非你真能见到  不然不会知道其中奥秘
Aha! you wouldn't knowow it works unless you can do it.
我做的事
What I can do
和与鬼魂下棋无关  傻子
Has nothing to do with chatting with ghosts, you nitwit.
这是种感觉  一种感应
It's a feeling, a sense.
人死后  大脑就不会运转
When somebody's dead, their brain stops functioning,
他们就不会说话
Which means there's no more talking.
只留下的记忆是他们的身份
There's just who they were
-还有他们死前的记忆  -这我也知道
- And whatever they knew before they died. - That's how it works for me.
好  我真为你感到高兴
Great. I'm happy for you.
你只是嫉妒我的本事比你强
You're just jealous my powers are better than yours.
这样吧
We're here.
闭上嘴  乖乖送你的三明治
Now shut the hell up and deliver your damn sandwiches.
他在这里干什么
What's he doing here?
他来给工作人员送午餐
Um, he came to deliver lunch to the work crew.
午餐  你的工作说明上要求你一个人来
Lunch? your instructions were to come alone.
别担心  我不会告诉别人死尸的事
Don't worry. I won't tell anyone about the body.
抱歉  先生
I'm sorry, sir.
-他在后车厢乱翻  然后就看到了  -兄弟
-He--he was rooting around in the back, and he saw it. - Dude.
我可以保密
I can keep a secret.
最好如此
Well, you'd better...
Hurley  如果你不愿在厨房工作
Hurley, 'cause if you think working in the kitchen is bad--
我喜欢在厨房工作
I like the kitchen.
你觉得北极熊的粪便味道怎样
Well, how do you feel about polar bear feces?
因为如果你敢泄露半个字
Because if you breathe one word of this,
我就把你运到长蛇岛
I'll have you shipped to hydra island
你就可以给那些可笑的实验品称粪便了
So you can weigh turds for their ridiculous experiments.
你们俩
You two!
把包裹抬进去
Get the package inside.
你呢  呆在这里等我回来
And you? stay here till I get back.
-你自认为可以处理这些吗  -是  先生
- You think you can handle that? - Yes, sir.
兄弟  那家伙真是个杂种
Dude, that guy's a total douche.
-你不适合干  -那杂种是我爸
- You are not qualified to be... - That douche is my dad.
你真的说过要带我去吃饭
You did say you were taking me out to dinner.
不  我说我要带你去家餐馆
No, I said I was taking you to a restaurant.
亲爱的  想告诉我这儿藏着什么吗
You wanna tell me what's back here, sweetheart?
你的面试
Your audition.
不管这里发生了什么
Look, whatever you got going on here,
都不关我的事
This isn't really my thing.
Miles  就我了解的来看
From what I understand, Miles,
如果价格足够高的话  这正是你的工作
If the price is right, this is exactly your thing.
那么关于这个人你能告诉些我什么呢
So what can you tell me about this man?
他叫Felix
His name's Felix.
他当时正在
He was...
去送东西的路上
On his way to deliver something to, uh...
交给一个叫Wildmore的人
A guy named... Widmore.
送什么呢
Deliver what?
一堆纸  照片  图画什么的
A bunch of papers, photos, pictures...
都是关于
Of...
挖空的坟墓
Empty graves.
还有一张买一架旧飞机的
A purchase order...
购货单
For an old airplane.
那么
So...
我的工作完成了吗
Did I pass?
我正要带领一次探险  去一座岛屿
I'm leading an expedition to an island,
而岛上有那么一个人
And on the island is a man that
我们很难找到他
Will be very difficult to find.
-所以我需要你  -需要我干什么呢
- That's why I need you. - Need me for what?
岛上有一群死去的人
This island has a number of deceased individuals...
他们以前住在那里  正是这个人
Residing on it, and as this man is
要为他们的遇害负上全责
The one responsible for their being deceased.
我们确信关于那个人的下落
We believe they can supply invaluable information
这群尸体可以给我们很多珍贵的线索
As to his where abouts.
听起来就和去捕获一个杀人魔
As much as hunting down a mass murderer
一样安全
Sounds really safe,
呃  我弃权
Uh, I'm...I'm gonna pass.
谢谢这个面试的机会
Thanks for the audition.
我老板愿意支付你160万美金
My employer is willing to pay you $1.6 million dollors.
何时出发呢
When do we leave?
总之
So anyway...
-我不想讨论这个  -你开玩笑吧
- I don't want to talk about it. - Are you kidding me?
你父亲是那些影片里面的那个人
How weird is it that your dad is
这听起来多怪异啊
That dude from all those movies.
那时他叫做Marvin Candle
Only back then, he was called Marvin Candle.
听起来像什么  别名吗
Was that, like, a stage name?
那名字叫  我不想讨论这个
What part of "I don't want to talk about it"
既然你不想讨论  那你为什么告诉我呢
Well, if you didn't want to talk about it, why'd you tell me?
你知道他是你父亲多久了
How long have you known he was your dad?
我们到这儿的第三天  我在餐厅排队
The third day we were here, I was on line at the cafeteria,
而我母亲排在我后面
And my mother got in line behind me.
那是我第一个线索
That was my first clue.
但是达摩组织的那些人最后都死了
But all those Dharma dudes end up dead.
难道你不想救他吗
Don't you wanna... save him?
我救不了他
I can't save him.
不管我如何补救  他们都会杀了他
They're gonna get kill no matter what I do,
那么何必麻烦呢
So why bother?
我要你们送我去Radzinsky的工作地点
I need you to take me to Radzinsky at the work site
现在就走
Immediately.
你
You...
Hurley
Hurley...
-只要你透露一个字  -尸骨无存  我明白
- You say a word... - Polar bear poop. Got it.
尸体是怎么处理的呢
What happened to the body?
哪有尸体
What body?
该我来打扫这间子  你在这干什么呢
This room is on my rounds. What are you doing here?
我以为来替你的班
I figured I'd cover for ya.
我听说了你儿子的事
I heard what happened to your son.
哪部分呢  是他中了枪
Which part...That he got shot
还是在医务室被绑架呢
Or that someone kidnapped him from the infirmary?
那你还来这儿干活
Then what are you doing here at work?
我还能干什么呢
What else am I gonna do?
坐在一边祈祷那群笨蛋会找到我孩子吗
Sit around and pray that those idiots are gonna find my boy?
你可以走了
So you can get outta here.
你和那个叫Kate的女人
You came in here a couple days
前几天一起来的  对吧
Ago with that woman Kate, right?
对
Yeah.
你了解她吗
You know her at all?
为什么这么问呢
Why?
因为她说了些
'cause she's got some...
怪异的话  关于我的孩子
Kinda weird thing for my kid.
先是她出现医务室里
First, she shows up at the infirmary
给我孩子输血
And gave him blood.
然后当他失踪后
But then when he goes missing,
她却过来跟我说
She comes to me and she says,
别担心  你孩子会没事的
"Don't worry. He's gonna be okay."
我想告诉你
I'm gonna tell you somethin', man.
我开始认为
I'm beginning to think
她可能和这些事情有关
That she's got something to do with this.
我该去找Horace
I should go to Horace,
举报她
Report her.
你说呢
What do you think?
我想 呃  Roger
I think, Roger, that, uh,
你今天很倒霉
That you've had a hell of a day, and that's...
所以你喝醉了酒
Given you a very good excuse to go out and get drunk.
才想出这些荒唐的事
Maybe that's put some...some crazy ideas into your head.
我了解那个女人  Kate
I know that woman, Kate.
她是我朋友
She's my friend,
她也绝不会去伤害你儿子
And she would never do anything to hurt your son.
应该吧
Sure.
我是新来了  张博士
So I'm new here, Dr. Chang.
-你们在兰花站干嘛呢  -这是机密
- What is it exactly you do at the orchid? - It's classified.
真的吗  那你不能透露给任何人咯
Oh, really? You can't tell anyone?
即使是你老婆
Not even your wife?
不能
No.
那告诉你的孩子吗
What about your kids?
我儿子才三个月大  所以我还没告诉他
I have a 3-monthld son, so, no, I haven't told him.
三个月吗  哇  恭喜啊
3 months? Wow! Congrats.
他叫什么呢
What's his name?
Miles
Miles.
无巧不成书啊
Small world.
那也是你的名字吧  Miles
That's your name, too. right, Miles?
是啊
Yeah.
那你是爵士乐迷吗  张博士
So are you a fan of jazz, Dr. Chang?
喜欢Miles Davis吗
Like Miles Davis?
我老婆喜欢
My wife is.
我喜欢乡村乐
I like country.
你们俩来这里有三年了吧
So you two have been here for... three years now.
关系应该很亲密吧
Must be pretty tight, huh?
我和张博士不在同一个生活圈
Dr. chang and I... don't exactly travel in the same circles.
我不知道有哪些生活圈
I wasn't aware there were circles.
太好了
Great.
我们应该抽空一起去喝几杯
We should all... get together for a beer sometime.
这主意很酷吧
How awesome would that be happy?
这儿停一下
Stop here.
你们不必等我了  我和Radzinsky回去
You don't need to wait. I'll get a ride back with Radzinsky.
老兄  这是什么地方
Dude, what is this place?
这么隐蔽干什么呢
And what's up with all the secrecy?
我不知道  也不关心
Don't know. Don't care.
喂  Glenn
Hey, Glenn!
积载表上的序列号说多少呢
What's the serial number that goes on the hatch list?
4  8...
4, 8...
15...
16...
23...
等一会  纸有些脏
Hold on a minute. it's smudged.
-42  -42
- 42. - 42.
你是怎么知道的呢
How the hell did you know that?
因为他们在造我们的舱
'cause they're building our hatch.
什么舱呢
What hatch?
弄得我们坠机的那个舱
The one that crashed our plane.
谢谢
Thanks.
嘿  Miles
Hey, miles.
我们认识吗
Do I know you?
Miles  我叫Bram
Miles, my name's Bram.
你欠我一份烤鱼卷
You owe me a fish taco.
很抱歉  但他们在监视你的公寓
Sorry about that, but your apartment's being watched,
我们在尽全力来
And we had to try our best
说服你不要为Charle Widmore工作
To talk you out of working for Charles Widmore.
我不知道那是谁
I have no idea who that is.
他特别资助的一艘船
He's the man
而你下周就要参加船员
Who chartered the boat you'll be getting on next week.
朋友  你不会想上那条船
And, my friend, you do not want to get on that boat.
你知道雕像的阴影里藏着什么吗
Do you know what lies in the shadow of the statue?
不知道
No, can't say that I do.
那就说明你没准备好去那座岛
Then you're not ready to go to that island.
但如果你跟我们一起
But if you come with us--
你会发现你毕生寻找的答案
All those things you've spent your life trying to find out?
你全会知道的
You'll know.
你会知道你到底是谁  Miles
You'll know who you are, Miles
为什么你有那种能力
Why it is you have a gift,
更重要的是
And most of all,
你会知道你父亲
You'll know about your father.
我不知道你从哪得到的情报
I don't know where you've been getting your intel,
但我很久之前就不关心我的父亲了
But I stopped caring about my father a long time ago.
我关心的仅仅是钱
What I do care about is money.
我告诉你为什么
So I'll tell you what.
你要我不去小岛
You want me to pass on going to the island?
那你得给我他们愿意付的钱的双倍
It's gonna cost you double what they offered
320万美元
$3.2 million.
我们不会付给你任何东西
We're not paying you anything.
就算有这世上所有的钱
But all the money in the world
也无法填补你内心对你父亲所失去的感觉 Miles
Isn't gonna fill that empty hole inside you, Miles.
这很伤人心  不是吗
That's sad, isn't it?
把他扔下去
Toss him!
你选错边了
You're playing for the wrong team.
那你这又是什么队伍啊
Yeah? What team are you on?
一个稳赢的队伍
The one that's gonna win.
他们在建的那舱
That hatch they're building?
将会发生场事故的
There's gonna be an accident,
然后他们还会安个计算机
Then they're gonna have to build a computer
有个按钮  你必须按  不然这世界将会毁灭
With a button you have to push so the world doesn't end.
你爸爸
So your dad...
他还在...
Is he around...
...我们来的时间 未来
You know, when we came from? the future?
不
No.
这对你来讲不是很棒
Well, then this is kind of awesome for you, huh?
怎么会让我觉得很棒
How is it awesome?!
因为你可以和他经常在一起
Because you get to hang out with him,
你可以了解更多有关他的东西
You know, get to know him better and stuff.
不用谢我了
And don't bother thanking me,
但他完全沉湎于啤酒中了  老兄
But he was totally down for that beer, dude.
也许他会让你抱着婴儿时期的你
You know, and maybe he'll let you hold baby you,
给你自己换尿布或者...
Or you can change your own diaper or--
听清楚
Listen up,
这种谈话仅此一次
'cause we're only gonna have this conversation once.
我不想和我爸一起
I don't want to hang out with my dad.
我不想更了解他  或者"其它的事"
I don't want to know him better and "stuff."
为什么不想
Why not?
你小的时候他一直打你吗
Did he beat you up when you were little or something?
我小的时候他甚至都不在我身边  你这傻子
He wasn't even around when I was little, you dimwit!
我现在才对他有所了解
I never knew him until now.
我怎么会告诉你这些
Why am I even telling you this?
因为你很痛苦  你想摆脱这种痛苦
'cause you're in pain and you need to let it out.
我不痛苦  这无关紧要
I'm not in pain. it doesn't matter.
我爸死了  他离开了  他从不关心我
My father is dead. he's gone. he never cared about me,
我无法去改变这种状况
And nothing I can do will ever change that.
但他没死  我们刚刚才把他放下车
But he's not gone. we just dropped him off.
你想扯入我家这事吗
You want to get into my business?
-管好你自己的事吧  -把这书还给我
- Let's get into yours!  - Give that back to me.
-让我读下这日记怎样  -这不是日记  是隐私
- How about we read your little diary?  -It's not a diary! It's personal!!
看看在这比你生命还重要的书里有些什么
Let's see what's going on in that piece of granite you call a head
把  把这个还我
Give that-- give that back to me.
-还给我  -在胡斯(星战里的星球)的外部
- Give it back!  - "exterior--hoth.
"一个小型机械人飞速从外太空降落"
"a little spy robot thingy zips through the atmosphere
"撞上了这颗白雪皑皑的星球"
"and crashes into the snowy planet below.
"这时Chewbacca常出现了
"that's when Chewbacca shows up
用他的激光箭把它给炸毁了"
and blasts it away with his crossbow laser.
"他摇动着他的'匹'拳在空中挥舞"
"he shakes his fury fist in the sky in triumph.
Chewbacca--raaar."
是"毛"
It's "furry."
"毛拳"  我要检查下拼写了
"furry fist." I need to spell-check it.
这是什么鬼东西
What the hell is this?
我在写"帝国反击战"
I'm writing "empire strikes back."
不好意思  什么东西
Uh... I'm sorry. what?
1977年  对吧
It's 1977, right?
《星球大战》刚上映
So "Stars Wars" just came out.
很快  George Lucas
And pretty soon, George Lucas
就会找寻续集的剧本
is gonna be looking for a sequel.
我看了《帝国》差不多200次了
I've seen "empire," like, 200 times,
所以我在想
So I figured
让事情变简单点  把构思送给他
I'd make life easier and send him the script...
顺便帮他改良一下
With a couple improvements.
这是我有生以来见到过的最蠢的事
That has gotta be the stupidest thing I've ever heard.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
至少我不怕和我父亲谈话
Well, at least I'm not scared to talk to my own dad.
-James  你回来了  -差不多吧
- James. you're back. - Barely.
回想起当时你还记得
You ever had one of those days you feel like
那个荷兰小男孩把你的手指...
The little Dutch boy with your finger in the...
大夫  你好啊
Doc. hey.
发生什么事了
What's going on?
Ben的父亲认为Kate和他儿子的失踪
Ben's father thinks that Kate had something to do
有关
with his son going missing.
他怎么会这样想
Why the hell would he think that?
因为她和他聊过天  希望能让他好受点
Because she talked to him, tried to make him feel better.
她的心地是很好的
Her heart was in the right place.
可是她真的很没脑
Yeah, well, where was her head?
我和Roger谈过了
I had a talk with Roger.
我认为他还没和别人说过任何事
I don't think he's gonna say anything to anyone for now.
我只是想让你知道
I just wanted you to know.
-谢谢你告诉我这些  大夫  -不客气
-Thanks for filling me in, doc.  - No problem.
老板
Hey, boss.
我们有些情况  你最好来一趟办公室吧
We got a development. you better come to the office.
Phil  我一整天都在丛林中东奔西走着
Phil, I've been running around the jungle all day,
所以无论有什么情况都应该让我休息下
So whatever developments you got can wait a while.
我知道谁带走了小孩
I know who took the kid.
是谁
Yeah? who's that?
是你
You.
我能解释清楚
Got a perfectly good explanation for what you saw on that tape.
那就说吧
I sure as hell hope so.
你和Horace谈过了没
You talk to Horace yet?
没  我认为经过三年的共事
No. I thought that after three years of working together,
你不会亏待我的
I'd give you the benefit of the doubt--
拿绳子来
Get some rope.
Gray先生
Mr. Gray?
希望你别介意  大门开着的
I hope you don't mind. your gate was open.
Straume先生  没问题的  不要紧
Mr. Straume. of course. of course. no problem.
你怎么来了
What, uh, what brings you by?
先生
Well, sir, uh...
我就要去乘船旅行段时间了
I'm about to go on a boat trip for a while,
另外...
And...
我要把这个还给你
I wanted to give this back to you
我欺骗了你  Gray先生
I lied to you, Mr. Gray.
我无法和你儿子对话
I wasn't able to talk to your son.
你为什么告诉我这些
Why are you telling me this?
你完全可以让我深信你之前说的那些话
You could have just let me go on believing what you said.
-那对你的儿子很不公平  -什么意思
- That wouldn't have been fair to your son. - I'm sorry?
如果你想让你儿子知道你深爱着他
If you needed your son to know that you loved him,
你应该在他还活着的时候就告诉他
You should've told him when he was still alive.
我说你害怕跟你父亲说话  对此我很抱歉
Sorry I said you were afraid to talk to our dad, dude.
别放在心上
Don't worry about it.
我以前也曾恨过我爸
I used to hate my dad, too.
在我10岁的时候他离开了
He left when I was 10.
但好在我给了他第二次机会
But the best thing I ever did was give him a second chance.
我们成为了最好的朋友
We got to be the best of friends,
尽管我有可能再也见不到他了
And although I may never see him again,
我很想念他
I miss him.
而且我知道一样会在想我的
And I know he feels the same.
我爸爸不是在我10岁的时候离开的
My dad didn't leave when I was 10.
我那时还是个婴儿  我不记得他了
I-I was a baby. I never knew him.
我也不想记得他
And I don't want to.
就是这样子
It's that happening.
那是Luke的态度
That was Luke's attitude,too.
什么意思
What?
在《帝国》里  Luke发现Vader是他的父亲
In "empire," Luke found out Vader was his father,
但没有拿开他的光剑
But instead of putting away his lightsaber
让大家有一个交流的机会
And talking about it,
反而因为反应过度把他的手给切断了
He overreacted and got his hand cut off.
我是说  他们最后还是和解了  但代价很大
I mean, they worked it out eventually, but at what cost?
另外颗死星被摧毁了
Another death star was destroyed,
Boba Fett被Sarlacc给吃掉了
Boba Fett got eaten by the Sarlacc,
然后出现了Ewoks族人
And we got the Ewoks.
这些都可以避免
It all could've been avoided
如果他们能有所交流
If they'd just, you know, communicated.
面对这些  Ewoks不是东西  老兄
And let's face it. the Ewoks sucked, dude.
你好  等一下
Hello? Oh, one moment.
是找你的
It's for you.
Miles吗  我需要你
Miles? I need you.
你需要我?
You do?
潜艇从总部开来了
Sub's here from H.Q.
我需要你把他们带回来
I need your help bringing them in.
好的  是新成员吗
Sure. new recruits?
不是的  是从安娜堡市来的科学家
No, uh, scientists from Ann Arbor.
去开车吧  我们去码头
Get your van, and let's get to the dock.
要帮忙吗
Hey, can I get a hand with this?
好的
Yeah, yeah, sure.
-Dan  -你好啊  Miles
- Dan.  - Hey, Miles.
好久不见了
Long time no see.